[machines whirring]
Oh! This is the foundation I wanted!
And this lipstick, this spray-on manicure.
Ooh! [giggles] And this wig is so cute!
[Melody]
Um, boss? We really should get going soon.
[Neon] Just a second!
I want this camisole too.
[sighing] All this shopping's
gonna be the death of me.
I agree.
[theme song playing]
Is there anything else I should buy
while we're here?
What about you, Eliza?
Do you want anything?
Oh, no, I'm fine, thank you.
[indistinct chatter]
[Neon] I'm going to the restroom.
Don't worry, just watch my stuff, okay?
What do you think?
Will Kurapika be okay?
I certainly hope so.
My flute should have helped alleviate
his fatigue, at least a little.
This assassination…
How do you feel about it?
The Ten Dons will hire pros
to handle the Troupe.
Sir?
And so, I want you
to join the assassin team.
Judging by the pace of his heartbeat,
he wasn't all that happy about it.
I don’t believe he wanted
to join the assassin team.
Of course, he didn't.
But as you well know,
Kurapika is extremely determined.
And he is willing to sacrifice everything
if it means that he's able
to achieve his desired goal.
Not an easy road to walk.
I couldn't live that way.
A life where you’re basically killing
yourself? What’s the point?
It's been a while. I hope she's all right.
Once we finish this job,
I'm cashing out and seeing the world
on my bike.
That does sound delightful.
[Basho] Not enjoying life is a crime.
[Melody] There are many ways to live.
Not everyone has the same ideas
about what's important.
[whimpering]
-[Basho] Huh?
-[Melody] Something wrong?
The boss is gone!
-Wait, what?
-[gasps]
[Neon] Daddy's a big liar!
He wasn't going to take me to the auction!
And he promised and everything!
Fine, then, I'll just go by myself!
[knocking on door]
[Zenji] Come in.
[door opening]
[Zenji] One, two, three, four, five, six.
It looks like everyone is here.
[Mafioso] No, not yet.
What? I thought the team
had eight members.
Nostrade is sending over
one additional person.
Ugh! That brown-noser
with the fake fortune-telling, eh?
[Zenji]
Alright, we got everyone all together?
Your mission is to wipe out
the Phantom Troupe.
When the auction kicks off again tonight,
they may come out of hiding.
If they do, eliminate them
any way you see fit.
So, all of us are going
after the same target?
We should pick out some code names
to use for each other.
Let's use colors.
You can just call me "Blue."
I'll be Red.
It's like a game, isn't it?
Hmm? What about you?
-[Silva] Silva.
-[Zeno] Zeno.
Zeno huh? What color's that?
[Zeno] We will both use our real names.
You will?
You're welcome to call me by my name,
but I won't take orders.
We'll do this our own way.
Hold on. Silva and Zeno?
Like, of the Zoldyck family?
[Kurapika gasps]
[Zeno]
Let me know if you want someone killed.
You get 30 percent off
for being in the same industry.
[all gasping]
[Kurapika] So, they're Killua's family.
We could use code names
but does it matter?
He has a point. There's no rule
that says we have to work together.
But we're talking about the Troupe, here.
Attacking alone will be dangerous.
And you?
Sloppy teamwork will only serve
to cause confusion.
I’ll be fine by myself.
[chuckles] It's five to four.
There you go.
[Zenji] The auction begins at 9:00.
We'll escort you to the auction hall.
Wait here till it's time.
[door opening]
[Zenji] Hey, Nostrade.
How do you feel, my friend?
Not too bad, huh?
You're a big shot now, aren't ya?
Not too long ago, you were just
heading up a small country gang,
and now, you're acting
like you're my equal.
I hear that you've been wringing
your hands so much,
your skin's rubbed off.
You sure you're okay? [cackles]
Jealousy among men is pathetic.
Bastard!
What the hell is this, you little punk?
If you want a piece of me, go ahead!
[Nostrade] Kurapika, that's enough!
Get one thing straight.
No one is impressed by you, do ya hear me?
[Nostrade] Many resent my success
because they're unaware
of their own incompetence.
But I plan to continue my rise to the top
using Neon's fortune-telling.
I'm depending on you too, Kurapika.
You will be rewarded generously, in time.
Yes, sir.
[whistle blowing]
[Kurapika] Are the police helping you?
[Nostrade] 60 percent of the votes
for the Yorknew City mayor's election
were bought.
And the police chief
is the mayor's lap dog.
Imposing traffic restrictions is simple.
[phone ringing]
Yes, hello?
[Melody]
Kurapika, bad news. The boss ran away!
She changed clothes
when she went to the restroom,
so she must have planned ahead.
Don't worry. I think I might know
where she went.
Go back to the hotel and stand by.
-What now?
-Your daughter has run away.
She what? [coughing]
She'll likely head to our destination.
[Nostrade] The auction?
[dialing number]
Hmm. Damn, she turned off her cellphone.
But Neon doesn't even have a pass
to the auction.
They'll turn her away
when she reaches the checkpoint.
This is Light Nostrade.
I need for you to get an order
to the guards at the gate.
If a girl around 17 or 18 tries to enter
without a pass, take her into custody.
Her description...
You're all set.
Thanks, you can go ahead now.
Phew! I didn't know how to get
through that gate, so...
Thanks a lot for the help.
Happy to be of service.
[Nostrade] Really? When was that?
[policeman] About five minutes ago.
Her hair and clothes
were a little different,
but it was probably her.
[Nostrade] And she didn't have a pass?
To be perfectly honest, it didn't seem
to me like she even knew she needed one.
She mentioned something about
who her daddy was,
but then she just left.
Yes, she got into a taxi alone.
Right. Yes, sir.
That ought to do it.
[groans] Where could she have gone?
[Kurapika] I'll search for her.
Do you have a map of Yorknew city?
[Chrollo]
I've hear you're a good fortune-teller.
[Neon] Huh?
[Chrollo] Someone told me once.
I can't recall who.
[Neon] I am good. Important people
are always coming to me.
How accurate are you?
[Neon] They say I'm always right.
"They"? What do you mean?
Shouldn't the fortune-teller know?
[Neon] My hand moves on its own.
Oh, impressive.
Would you tell me mine?
Okay. Just write down your name,
your birthday and blood type,
and I'll take it from there.
Think this will work?
Let's see.
Your name's really Chrollo Lucilfer?
-What kind of name is that?
-Well, my friends just call me "Boss."
[giggles] Boss? Wow!
That's even weirder!
Okay, here goes.
[Kurapika] It appears your daughter
is already in the Cemetery Building
on the auction site.
She is? How is that possible?
Not sure, but we need to hurry.
There, all done.
Then, can I read it?
Yeah, sure.
My fortunes are kind of strange.
They're usually made up
of four or five poems.
Each one corresponds
to a week of that month,
so the first one might just be some stuff
that happened already.
Huh...
[Chrollo]
Forever set, a precious moon is lost.
The others mourn him with ceremony grand.
Rising up to heaven,
the mighty moon of frost...
with a melody from the mourning band.
[Chrollo] It's amazing. And correct.
About this first one...
Don't tell me, please! Really, I never
look at the fortunes I write.
Why not?
I just get the feeling they'll be a lot
more accurate if I don't get involved.
Then, would you mind
if I ask you a question?
Sure.
[Chrollo] This verse. It makes reference
to a requiem for the dead.
Do you believe in the afterlife, Neon?
Hmm...
I guess I don't. Not really.
Fortunes are only written
to help the living.
And in this case, that's you, Mr. Chrollo.
A requiem doesn’t help a dead person.
It comforts those who’re left behind.
That’s what I think, anyway.
And you're probably right.
Let's go. The auction preview
is about to start.
[Neon]
What I said, I heard from someone else.
[Chrollo] What?
[Neon] A fortune teller on TV
said it when I was little.
You know, about what I said before
about how
the purpose of fortunes
is to make the living people happy.
Oh.
And so, the fortune-teller tried really
hard to give negative fortunes to people.
Negative?
You see, that way, people would make
an effort to improve their lives.
and to avoid misfortune.
Back then, I can remember being
really inspired about how true that was.
That's when I decided
I would be a fortune-teller.
[Chrollo]
Forever set, a precious moon is lost.
The others mourn him with ceremony grand.
Rising up to heaven, the mighty moon
of frost...
with a melody from the mourning band.
Harvest barren, wine-spilled
lovers slumber
beside the bloody Scarlet Eyes.
Though cut in half shall be your number,
'tis not lost wherein your advantage lies.
Amuse yourself with the entr’acte.
Seek out new friends once in a bind.
Perhaps to the east, one can be tracked.
The one most needed you're sure to find.
A few years later, that fortune-teller
ended up getting arrested for fraud.
-Do you mean the Galactic Matron?
-That's the one!
If memory serves,
she didn't believe in the afterlife.
She didn't, and that's why I don't believe
in it either.
[elevator dings]
[Chrollo]
Personally, I believe we have a soul.
[Neon] Hmm?
See, that's the reason I wanted to fulfil
my dead friends' wish.
It's what he would have wanted.
What wish?
To wreak havoc.
[Chrollo] Are you okay?
Call a doctor, quickly!
First floor. We're over
by the north elevator.
Someone's sick. Call an ambulance.
We can't. There's no way they're gonna
let an ambulance come in here.
Not if they don't have an auction pass
on them.
You're kidding me. What if she dies?
What happens then, huh?
She's the daughter
of the Nostrade Family boss!
If she dies here, it's on your head,
understand?
[sighs] Yeah, I heard ya.
Some of the Ten Dons are big fans of hers.
We're on it. Just sit tight!
Hey, call for an ambulance!
[man] Right!
Hey, tell me something.
Can you rewind what' on this monitor?
Hmm? Sure.
[assassin] The swiftest chop.
Anyone else would have missed it.
I've missed this excitement.
[chuckles] I've found my prey.
Mr. Nostrade, your daughter is resting
in room 501 up on the fifth floor.
There's simply no way she could have
gotten her hands on a pass.
How did she get in?
[Kurapika] Your daughter's picture
is accessible on the Hunter website.
[Nostrade] What?
Most likely, someone located this picture
of her on the website,
found her and brought her here soon after.
[Nostrade growls]
I'll find that scum and kill him!
[Kurapika] Calm down, sir.
I don't think capturing your daughter
was their primary objective.
It's possible they used her as a hostage
in case they couldn't
get into the building.
[Nostrade grunts]
It's dangerous here,
so I've called Melody and Basho.
They'll be here soon.
Are you sure it's wise
to leave it to them?
[Kurapika]
You should stay with her too, sir.
[Nostrade] But... the auction!
-[Kurapika] There won't be one.
-Hmm?
This will be a battlefield.
The auction is sure to be canceled again.
[assassin] A trail of blood...
dripped on purpose.
Enough to be detected, smelled,
by one of the same breed.
We are the same, he and I.
We're predators.
Both addicted to killing.
[Chrollo] Don't worry.
I don't use cheap traps.
One-on-one?
Sounds good.
[Feitan] I have a message.
The boss said come
to the Cemetery Building and wreak havoc.
The Cemetery Building
is not too far from here.
Where are the others?
[Feitan] Thinking the same thing as us.
Cleaning up the trash
on the way to the building.
[Phinks] Okay, then let's go.
[Feitan] There's more.
The boss added an unusual rule this time.
Oh, yeah? What?
[Chrollo] Make it a big show.
[orchestral music playing]
[Chrollo]
Forever set, a precious moon is lost.
The others mourn him with ceremony grand.
Rising up to heaven, the mighty moon
of frost...
with a melody from the mourning band.
Harvest barren, wine spilled,
lovers slumber
beside bloody Scarlet Eyes.
Though cut in half your number,
'tis not lost wherein your advantage lies.
Amuse yourself with the entr’acte.
Seek new friends once in a bind.
Perhaps to the east, one can be tracked.
The one most needed...
you’re sure to find.
[assassin laughing]
Why, huh? Tell me why!
[laughs] Why?
Why am I alive? What's happening?
[Chrollo] This is an Indoor Fish.
A Nen fish that can only live
in enclosed spaces.
A carnivore that prefers human flesh.
You don't bleed or feel pain
as you're eaten.
You can't die until the Nen fish
disappears.
[assassin laughing] Won't die?
[moans]
[wind howling]
[breathes deeply]
[orchestral music playing]
[machine gun firing]
Forever set, a precious moon is lost.
The others mourn him with ceremony grand.
Rising up to heaven, the mighty moon
of frost...
with a melody from the mourning band.
Well, Uvo...
Can you hear it?
We dedicate this requiem to you.
[narrator]
It was the beginning of a stormy night,
that while fierce and drenched with blood,
was somehow overwhelmingly sad.
[orchestral music continues]
-[Gon] Coming up, Gon...
-[Killua]...and Killua's...
[both] Hunterpedia!
-I'm Gon!
-And I'm Killua!
[both] And this is our Hunterpedia!
Today, we're introducing Phinks,
a Troupe member.
And he's also an Enhancer.
He's strong enough to punch
straight through a body.
And sometimes, he dresses
in Egyptian clothing!
You're thinking of Sphinx!
[Gon] Next time,
"Assault x and x Impact."
[Killua] Oh, Gon.
Wherefore art thou, Gon?
[Gon] Killua, I'm Gon.
That's wherefore.
[Killua] Wait, that's it?